Get ready for what's coming.
Jackson Storm is part of the next
generation of high tech race.
Look at Jackson Storm.
Jackson Storm.
Jackson Storm in a class of his own.
Hey,
Cha, you got a good run.
You have no idea what a pleasure
it is for me to finally beat you.
Did you say meet or beat?
I think you you heard me.
Enjoy your retirement.
You'll never be the racer you once were.
You can't turn back the clock, kids,
but you can wind it up again.
The racing world is changing.
Treadmills into virtual reality.
Still working on that and
interactive race simulation.
You have jumped a barrier.
You are
going.
You have cash.
We got some work to do.
I am so excited that I get to train you.
Visualized feeding
the Beach ate me every week.
Veteran research.
Retires to make room for these
younger, faster research.
Have you given any thought
of retiree or no questions?
Pop out is.
You'Ll never be as fast as Storm.
But you can be smarter.
Good luck out there.
You're gonna need it.
I decide when I'm done.
You are not winning this.
I'm coming for you to warm it.